

# **EVA MARÍA PÉREZ FERNÁNDEZ**

GAME DESIGNER

+34 633 31 34 63 Madrid, Spain

emperezfe@gmail.com

Online portfolio

Itch.io

LinkedIn

#### ABOUT ME

Game designer with almost 5 years of experience working in the games industry. I consider myself a curious, committed and ever-adapting designer, willing to learn and to give my best in every project I participate in. I deeply enjoy bringing ideas to life working hand in hand with other developers in a team. In my free time I develop my own projects and participate in game jams.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Game Designer

Tequila Works | January 2023 - Current

- Worked on unannounced AAA adventure project since concept phase to production. Designed mechanics, systems, and combat.
- Prototyped several systemic puzzles, mechanics and features using Unreal Engine 5 blueprints.
- Designed and implemented AI (enemies and NPCs) using Behavior Trees.
- Systems design, balance and tweaking. Proficiency creating balance spreadsheets.

# Kids Game Designer

Lingokids | September 2020 - January 2023

- Designed more than 10 educational games, merging them with action, adventure and puzzle elements, published in the Lingokids app. Prototyping using Unity (C#).
- Conducted thorough data analysis and user testing.

#### VR/AR Designer and Developer

Spika Tech | September 2018 - February 2019

- Narrative and interface design in VR. VR prototyping (UE4).
- Design and development of AR application for a museum (Unity, Vuforia).

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Master in Video Game Design

UCM | October 2019 - June 2020

Master's Thesis: Video game project in a multidisciplinary team of 25 people.

# Degree in Video Game Design and Development

URJC | September 2015 - September 2019

#### **SKILLS**

- Most used game engines:
  - Unreal Engine 5
  - Unity
- Some experience in other engines (GameMaker, Godot)
- 2D software: Photoshop, Illustrator
- 3D software: 3DSMax, Blender
- Documentation: GDocs, Confluence
- Spreadsheets: Excel, GSheets
- Data analysis: Power BI

# **LANGUAGES**

### **English**